# Connor M. Flynn

839 Ridgedale, Birmingham, MI 48009

## Summary

Over five years experience in e-commerce operations and two years as a lead UI/UX frontend designer. Proven technology and project management skills shown through successful product launches and technical support. Strong capabilities demonstrated in creative skills by award-winning video and design projects.

## **Education**

DePaul University, Chicago, IL 2012 - 2016

Business Major with Marketing concentration, Minor Digital Cinema

GPA: 3.7/4.0

# **Relevant Work Experience**

# Carhartt - Outerwear Apparel Company, Detroit, MI

UX Designer / Developer

May 2019 - Feb 2020

- Designed wireframes for unique e-commerce experiences and helped execute them into production code.
- Created reusable front-end content following existing brand guidelines while utilizing the BEM CSS methodology.
- Demonstrated ability to take mockups and translate them to pixel-perfect recreations in HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Tested content against browsers, operating systems, and devices to ensure consistent and accessible experiences.
- Exhibited intrapreneur traits while working on an agile team launching a new product within an established brand.

## Joey Pecoraro - Touring Music Producer, Detroit, MI

Video Graphic Design Partner & Tour Manager

October 2017 - May 2019

- Shot and edited music videos for YouTube influencers with modern production equipment and Adobe Suite.
- Designed promotional material and retail content (Merch / Vinyl) in Illustrator and Photoshop.

#### Flashtalking - Ad Serving, Measuring and Technology Company, Chicago, IL

**Publisher Certification Specialist** 

October 2016 - October 2017

- Internally and externally certified publishers (NBC, Apple News, ect) for ad serving with JS, HTML5, CSS, and video skills.
- Created HTML5, VAST, and VPAID ads to publisher's unique specifications and verified pixel tracking on placements.
- Handled technical communication and led calls with leading publishers, DSPs, ad networks, and measurement partners.
- Tested ad placements across mobile, tablet, and desktop fixing bugs or issues against publishing website's code stack.

#### Gallerique – Global Online Art Marketplace, Chicago, IL

Data & Marketing Associate

October 2014 - October 2016

----

- Managed an operations team of 3 to insure product uploads with clean integration into the website's front-end.
- Uploaded and maintained galleries' inventories of over 1000 pieces through knowledge of Excel, Magento, and HTML.

... . . . .

Software	Languages / Frameworks	Web / Operating Systems	CMS Experience
Photoshop	HTML5	Git	Salesforce Commerce
Illustrator	CSS	Linux Shell	IBM Websphere
After Effects	JavaScript / React.js	Macintosh	Magento
Premiere	Node.js / Express	Windows	Shopify
XD	Firebase	create-react-app	Wordpress
Sketch		Magento / Shopify /	SquareSpace
		WebSphere / WordPress	